[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "In each of the following questions, out of the given alternatives, choose the one that best expresses the meaning of the given word:- Sporadic",
    "options": ["Consistent", "Uniform", "Frequent", "Scattered"],
    "answer": "Scattered"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "In each of the following questions, out of the given alternatives, choose the one that best expresses the meaning of the given word:- Omnipotent",
    "options": ["Feeble", "Impotent", "Vulnerable", "Supreme"],
    "answer": "Supreme"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "In each of the following questions, choose the word opposite in meaning to the given word:- Repeal",
    "options": ["Abolish", "Annul", "Enact", "Nullify"],
    "answer": "Enact"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "In each of the following questions, choose the word opposite in meaning to the given word:- Equity",
    "options": ["Integrity", "Bias", "Justice", "Uprightness"],
    "answer": "Bias"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "In each of the following questions, out of the four alternatives, choose the one which can be substituted for the given word/sentence:- A formal composition or speech expressing high praise of somebody-",
    "options": ["eulogy", "elegy", "caricature", "exaggeration"],
    "answer": "eulogy"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The word 'Shrug' indicating doubt or indifference is associated with-",
    "options": ["Head", "Forehead", "Shoulders", "Eyebrows"],
    "answer": "Shoulders"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "He is quite _ in dealing with people.",
    "options": ["imprudent", "diplomatic", "unsubtle", "impolite"],
    "answer": "diplomatic"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "They suffered much _ tornado had hit their village.",
    "options": ["until", "as if", "let alone", "since"],
    "answer": "since"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Choose the wrong sentence:",
    "options": [
      "They parted from one another suddenly",
      "The leader expressed himself forcibly",
      "The land is belonged to an old lady",
      "Mother bought me an ice-cream"
    ],
    "answer": "The land is belonged to an old lady"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Choose the wrong sentence:",
    "options": [
      "His failure resulted for lack of attention",
      "He was always arguing with his brother",
      "When will you write to him about your plan?",
      "Who was the boy you were all laughing at?"
    ],
    "answer": "His failure resulted for lack of attention"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Choose the correctly spelt word:-",
    "options": ["Volantory", "Volantary", "Voluntary", "Voluntory"],
    "answer": "Voluntary"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Choose the correctly spelt word:-",
    "options": ["Accilerate", "Accelerrate", "Accilarate", "Accelerate"],
    "answer": "Accelerate"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Choose the correctly spelt word:-",
    "options": ["Suname", "Tsunami", "Sunami", "Sunamce"],
    "answer": "Tsunami"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Which living in poverty, the poet had to _ a great deal of sufferings",
    "options": ["see through", "put up with", "pass by", "fall back"],
    "answer": "put up with"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Wordsworth introduced the readers _ a new kind of poetry.",
    "options": ["with", "at", "to", "by"],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "----- his earlier study,the professor's new study indicates a general warning trend in global weather.",
    "options": [
      "In contrast of",
      "In contrast by",
      "In contrast to",
      "In contrast as"
    ],
    "answer": "In contrast to"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Only those who are not serious to their success work by----and starts.",
    "options": ["fits", "every inch", "against time", "long odds"],
    "answer": "fits"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Of the four alternatives given below, choose the word/words that best fits into the underlined word given in the sentence: - One day 'women will have so long been denied them leisure, money and room to themselves.",
    "options": ["Spece", "Liberty", "Office", "Capacity"],
    "answer": "Liberty"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Crafty men condemn study,simple men admire them and wise men use them.Best alternative for the word--Condemn",
    "options": ["laud", "compliment", "acclaim", "denounce"],
    "answer": "denounce"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "To end in smoke-----",
    "options": [
      "To come to nothing",
      "To see fire",
      "To go through suffering",
      "To create fire"
    ],
    "answer": "To come to nothing"
  }
]
